Frosty's Winter Wonderland is a animation, family, tv
movie film directed by Arthur Rankin, Jr..
Years have passed since Frosty left for the North Pole, but his promise is kept when he
hears news of the first snowfall of the season, and decides to return.
Narrator, played by Andy Griffith.
Frosty the Snowman, played by Jackie Vernon.
Jack Frost, played by Paul Frees.
Crystal, played by Shelley Winters.
Parson Brown, played by Dennis Day.
Child, played by Shelly Hines.
Frosty's Winter Wonderland is a 1976 American animated Christmas television special and a standalone sequel to
the 1969 special Frosty the Snowman, produced by Rankin/Bass Productions and animated by Topcraft.
It is the second television special featuring the character Frosty the Snowman.
It returns writer Romeo Muller, character designer Paul Coker, Jr., music composer Maury Laws and actor Jackie Vernon as the voice of Frosty, while Andy Griffith stars as the narrator (replacing
Jimmy Durante, who had been incapacitated by a stroke three years prior and retired from acting) with the rest of the cast consisting of Shelley Winters, Dennis Day and Paul Frees.
The special premiered on ABC on December 2, 1976.
The film explores themes of holiday, snowman, christmas.